<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<fmg>
<compression>None</compression>
<version>DarkSouls3</version>
<bigendian>False</bigendian>
<entries>
<text id="71000000">What, still here?</text>
<text id="71000001">Hand it over. That thing, your dark soul.</text>
<text id="71000002">For my lady's painting.</text>
<text id="71000100">Ahh, is this the blood?</text>
<text id="71000101">The blood of the dark soul?</text>
<text id="71000200"></text>
<text id="71000300"></text>
<text id="71000400"></text>
<text id="72000000">Ashen One, thy gift of flame has taken root</text>
<text id="72000001">And Uncle Gael will soon bring the pigment.</text>
<text id="72000002">Pigment coloured like the dark soul of man.</text>
<text id="72000100">I wonder if Uncle Gael has found it?</text>
<text id="72000101">The pigment coloured like the dark soul of man...</text>
<text id="72000200">My thanks, Ashen One.</text>
<text id="72000201">With this will I paint a world. </text>
<text id="72000202">Please tell me thy name.</text>
<text id="72000203">I would name this painting after thee.</text>
<text id="72000300">My thanks. I will paint a world of that name.</text>
<text id="72000301">Twill be a cold, dark, and very gentle place.</text>
<text id="72000302">And one day, it will make someone a goodly home.</text>
<text id="72000400">I see. We are much alike.</text>
<text id="72000401">Twill be a cold, dark, and very gentle place.</text>
<text id="72000402">And one day, it will make someone a goodly home.</text>
<text id="72000403">Then I will name this painting "Ash".</text>
<text id="72000500">I wonder when Uncle Gael intends his return.</text>
<text id="72000501">I hope the new painting will be to him a gentle home.</text>
<text id="72000600">My thanks, Ashen One.</text>
<text id="72000601">I will assuredly finish the painting.</text>
<text id="72000602">Of a cold, dark, and very gentle place.</text>
<text id="72000603">One day, it will make someone a goodly home.</text>
<text id="73000000">Oh, look at you, you've got your head screwed on correct.</text>
<text id="73000001">Fantastic. To meet a kindred spirit, on this godsforsaken crag.</text>
<text id="73000002">Call me Lapp. I can't remember my real name, so let's just go with that.</text>
<text id="73000003">I have a feeling we're going to make a fabulous team. Oh, you'll see, you'll see!</text>
<text id="73000004"></text>
<text id="73000100">Ohh, in all honesty there's something I should tell you...</text>
<text id="73000101">I'm...a Hollow. Yes, I try to play it off, but I haven't a clue about my past.</text>
<text id="73000102">Who I was, or what I lived for. Not even my own blessed name.</text>
<text id="73000103">That's why I've come here, searching.</text>
<text id="73000104">For the Purging Monument, said to be in the Ringed City,</text>
<text id="73000105">All I can say is... Those little stones aren't doing much to help me remember anymore...</text>
<text id="73000106"></text>
<text id="73000107">where the pygmies, who found the Dark Soul at the dawn of fire, reside.</text>
<text id="73000200">Well, that's the long and short of it.</text>
<text id="73000201">So, if I completely forget who you are, don't be wrath with me.</text>
<text id="73000202">C'mon, what else can I say? I'm a bloody Hollow, for heaven's sake.</text>
<text id="73000203"></text>
<text id="73000300">Oh, I know who you are.</text>
<text id="73000301">Great to see you still in once piece.</text>
<text id="73000302"></text>
<text id="73000303">Cor, I can see why they call this the dreg-heap at the world's end.</text>
<text id="73000304">...Mangled remnants from every age, and every land...</text>
<text id="73000305">It actually sort of lends credence to the old rumours.</text>
<text id="73000306">That the Ringed City rests below it all.</text>
<text id="73000400">Ah, don't mind me. You needn't worry yourself with this nonsense.</text>
<text id="73000401">I just wanted to tell someone, and I'm sick of old humpty. I should stay quiet.</text>
<text id="73000402">Wait, I'll make it up to you, by letting you in on a secret of sorts.</text>
<text id="73000403">Past here, you'll find the remains of a giant earthen tower half-submerged in a poisonous swamp.</text>
<text id="73000404">Not a very nice place to visit... Only, there's precious treasure in the thick of the swamp.</text>
<text id="73000405">I didn't have any use for it, you see. So sorry, I left the whole package behind.</text>
<text id="73000406">If I get the chance, I could go fetch it for you, but if that's too long to wait, go nab it for yourself.</text>
<text id="73000407">...I know who you are. A righteous warrior, yes? With a solemn duty, to boot. </text>
<text id="73000408">Well, grab that treasure, that's as good a duty as any.</text>
<text id="73000500">Oh, wait, I forgot to give you a wee warning.</text>
<text id="73000501">Watch out for the Dark Spirit lurking at the earthen tower.</text>
<text id="73000502">I'm hollow, so it won't bother me, but you're still human, I presume?</text>
<text id="73000503">Hmm, must be nice. Really, must be nice!</text>
<text id="73000504"></text>
<text id="73000600">Ohh, look at you, you found the treasure.</text>
<text id="73000601">Dashing, just dashing. You'll make good use of it, I'm sure.</text>
<text id="73000602">Now, this is a little toast, from me to you.</text>
<text id="73000603">Not much to speak of, but bottoms up. To the greatest warrior there is.</text>
<text id="73000604"></text>
<text id="73000700">Oh, there you are, perfect timing.</text>
<text id="73000701">You remember that treasure, in the thick of the poison swamp?</text>
<text id="73000702">Well, I fetched it for you, as promised.</text>
<text id="73000703">Oh, it was only a hop and a skip. I needed a rest from old nan over there.</text>
<text id="73000704">Here, go ahead, it's yours. Maybe it'll help you with that solemn duty of yours.</text>
<text id="73000705"></text>
<text id="73000800">This really is a dreg-heap at the world's end.</text>
<text id="73000801">...Mangled remnants from every age, and every land...</text>
<text id="73000802">It actually sort of lends credence to the old rumours.</text>
<text id="73000803">That the Ringed City rests below it all.</text>
<text id="73000900">Oh, well, fancy meeting you here.</text>
<text id="73000901">A true blessing, that we should seek the same place, and find ourselves standing here, together.</text>
<text id="73000902">I've got the last of my brew. Let's have our own little toast with it.</text>
<text id="73000903">To my search, and to your duty. And to the joy that lies before us.</text>
<text id="73000904">All right, then. Bottoms up!</text>
<text id="73000905"></text>
<text id="73001000">Now, I'm off in search of the Purging Monument.</text>
<text id="73001001">Once I find it, everything will come back to me.</text>
<text id="73001002">Who I was, what I lived for, what my name was.</text>
<text id="73001003">And... What terrible grudges I held.</text>
<text id="73001004">...I dunno, I just have this feeling. That that's the kind of man I was.</text>
<text id="73001005">Oh, don't hold it against me, I only think I was!</text>
<text id="73001006"></text>
<text id="73001100">Now, I'm off in search of the Purging Monument.</text>
<text id="73001101">Once I find it, everything will come back to me.</text>
<text id="73001200">Oh, and here we are again.</text>
<text id="73001201">How goes things? I'm rather running in circles, I'm afraid.</text>
<text id="73001202">I can't find the Purging Monument. And I've searched high and low...</text>
<text id="73001203">What if it was never here in the first place?</text>
<text id="73001204">Ah, bloody hell, what do I know...</text>
<text id="73001300">Sorry, I know it doesn't concern you...</text>
<text id="73001301">Seeing you all good and well, I...I just sort of spilled my guts to you.</text>
<text id="73001302">Just forget it all. Like a good Hollow would!</text>
<text id="73001303"></text>
<text id="73001400">...What did I come here in search of?</text>
<text id="73001401">...Damn, stop it, I'm unbreakable, unbreakable...</text>
<text id="73001500">...Ahh, please, someone tell me...</text>
<text id="73001501">..Who am I? Why am I here?</text>
<text id="73001600">Are you certain of that?</text>
<text id="73001601">No, sorry, I know you'd never lie to me.</text>
<text id="73001602">Thank you, thank you kindly. I'll speed right on over.</text>
<text id="73001603">...It won't be long now, before I know everything.</text>
<text id="73001604">Who I was, what I lived for, and what my name was.</text>
<text id="73001605">And I'll have you to thank for it all.</text>
<text id="73001700">Ahh, thank you, most sincerely.</text>
<text id="73001701">I swear upon my birth name.</text>
<text id="73001702">That I am your friend. No matter what might come out, no matter what I was.</text>
<text id="73001703">If you would do me the honour, allow me to be a true friend, always.</text>
<text id="73001800">...It won't be long now, before I know everything.</text>
<text id="73001801">Who I was, what I lived for, and what my name was.</text>
<text id="73001802">And I'll have you to thank for it all.</text>
<text id="73001900">Oh, finally, you've come.</text>
<text id="73001901">Now I know exactly who I was. And for that, I've a little thanks to be giving.</text>
<text id="73001902">Go this way, and peep past the broken staircase. Some awfully fine treasure's just sitting there all alone.</text>
<text id="73001903">It'll change your life...</text>
<text id="73002000">I've much to thank you for, so I'll say it again and again.</text>
<text id="73002001">Go this way, and peep past the broken staircase. Some awfully fine treasure's just sitting there all alone.</text>
<text id="73002002">What, don't you believe me?</text>
<text id="73002100">Every age, it seems, is tainted by the greed of men.</text>
<text id="73002101">Rubbish, to one such as I, devoid of all worldly wants!</text>
<text id="73002102"></text>
<text id="73002103">Hmmm, I dunno, maybe it's just the way we are.</text>
<text id="73002104">I'll stick you in my prayers. A fine dark soul, to you.</text>
<text id="73002200"></text>
<text id="73002201">What's wrong, friend?</text>
<text id="73002202">Stop it! Oh, please!</text>
<text id="73002203"></text>
<text id="73002204"></text>
<text id="73002300">Bloody hell! Lost your mind, have you?</text>
<text id="73002301">Then I have no choice! Forgive me!</text>
<text id="73002302"></text>
<text id="73002303"></text>
<text id="73002304"></text>
<text id="73002305"></text>
<text id="73002400"></text>
<text id="73002401">Perhaps...I deserved this...</text>
<text id="73002500">Forgive me, friend.</text>
<text id="73002501">I cannot die just yet.</text>
<text id="73002600"></text>
<text id="73002601">What in bloody hell?</text>
<text id="73002602">Stop that! Enough of that!</text>
<text id="73002603"></text>
<text id="73002604"></text>
<text id="73002700">Bloody hell, you've lost your head, have you?</text>
<text id="73002701">Then, let's have a go, shall we.</text>
<text id="73002702">I'm unbreakable! You can't crack me!</text>
<text id="73002703">I'll rot yer flesh!</text>
<text id="73002704"></text>
<text id="73002705"></text>
<text id="73002706"></text>
<text id="73002707"></text>
<text id="73002800"></text>
<text id="73002801">Curses, of all the luck...</text>
<text id="73002802">Everything always goes to pot, doesn't it...</text>
<text id="73002900">True friends, eh?</text>
<text id="73002901">Everything always goes to pot, doesn't it...</text>
<text id="74000000"></text>
<text id="74000100">Speak thee the name of God.</text>
<text id="74000101">Thine own god, if thou canst recall.</text>
<text id="74000200">Ahh, then thou'st not forgotten.</text>
<text id="74000201">Perhaps 'tis why we may converse.</text>
<text id="74000202">I am known as Shira, servant to the Princess Filianore, matriarch of the church.</text>
<text id="74000203">They who are ken to God's name are surely ken to the terrors of the dark.</text>
<text id="74000204">Please, I bid thee take not from the Princess her peace or rest.</text>
<text id="74000205">As the fire waneth, does she lie by the dark, all for the sake of Man.</text>
<text id="74000300">Thou'st a kind heart.</text>
<text id="74000301">To speak to a captive such as I.</text>
<text id="74000302">It is no surprise thou rememb'rest our God.</text>
<text id="74000400">May I ask thee a kindness?</text>
<text id="74000401">Perhaps thou'st beheld the lone dragon that inhabiteth this city?</text>
<text id="74000402">Midir is his name, and the Archdragons are his forebears.</text>
<text id="74000403">He once railed against the dark, but was by dark afflicted. Now here, returned, he remaineth.</text>
<text id="74000404">To watch over the sleeping Princess, true to the old accord.</text>
<text id="74000405">...And yet, I would have thee put the dragon to rest.</text>
<text id="74000406">Afore the dark consumeth him, and his vows are forgot.</text>
<text id="74000500">I offer my sincerest gratitude, thou who art ken to God's name.</text>
<text id="74000501">Please, take this.</text>
<text id="74000502">I have asked a thing most terrible of thee. May this token of thanks be of aid.</text>
<text id="74000600">I beg of thee, put the great dragon to rest.</text>
<text id="74000601">Afore the dark consumeth him, and his vows are forgot.</text>
<text id="74000700">As I thought. Such memories were lost by thy kind, long ago.</text>
<text id="74000701">And so it is ye...who yearn for darkness.</text>
<text id="74000800">Give thy memory a nudge.</text>
<text id="74000801">And name thee thy God.</text>
<text id="74000900">Very well. Then hasten on thy journey.</text>
<text id="74000901">Only, disturb not the sleeping Princess.</text>
<text id="74000902">As the fire waneth, does she lie by the dark, all for the sake of Man.</text>
<text id="74001000">Carest thou to speak thy peace?</text>
<text id="74001001">Hast thou mine entreaty reconsidered?</text>
<text id="74001100">So, Midir hath into the chasm fallen.</text>
<text id="74001101">Still, his voice I hear. The dark grieveth him yet.</text>
<text id="74001102">I prithee, put him to rest.</text>
<text id="74001103">Afore the dark consumeth him, and his vows are forgot.</text>
<text id="74001200">Just afore the church of the Princess standeth a tower, honouring ancient knights.</text>
<text id="74001201">There lieth a small shrine, behind the sculpted knight which beareth no arms.</text>
<text id="74001202">Tis from there one may descend the chasm of darkness.</text>
<text id="74001203">I prithee, put the great dragon to rest.</text>
<text id="74001300">I know, I have asked of thee a thing most terrible.</text>
<text id="74001301">Forgive me, thou wert but mine only hope.</text>
<text id="74001302">I prithee, put the great dragon to rest.</text>
<text id="74001303">Afore the dark consumeth him, and his vows are forgot.</text>
<text id="74001304">Just afore the church of the Princess standeth a tower built to honour ancient knights. Behind the sculpted knight which beareth no arms,</text>
<text id="74001305">is a small shrine, from which one may descend the chasm of darkness.</text>
<text id="74001400">My most humble thanks.</text>
<text id="74001401">Tis thanks to thee the dragon erred not from his vows.</text>
<text id="74001402">Please, take this. A final gift of thanks.</text>
<text id="74001403">Now, hasten on thy journey, but wake not the slumbering Princess.</text>
<text id="74001404">As the fire waneth, does she lie by the dark, all for the sake of Man.</text>
<text id="74001500">My humblest thanks.</text>
<text id="74001501">Now, hasten on thy journey, but wake not the slumbering Princess.</text>
<text id="74001502">As the fire waneth, does she lie by the dark, all for the sake of Man.</text>
<text id="74001600">Oh! Thou'rt now a spear of the church!</text>
<text id="74001601">What a wonderful, blessed day this is.</text>
<text id="74001602">With a spear such as thee, surely the Princess will slumber most gently, and Midir's vows will be honoured.</text>
<text id="74001603">I must thank thee, as a servant of the Princess, and a dear friend to Midir.</text>
<text id="74001604">May thy travels be resplendent with glory.</text>
<text id="74001700">As the fire waneth, does she lie by the dark, but now with thee to shelter her sleep.</text>
<text id="74001701">Bless ye spears of the church. May thy travels be resplendent with glory.</text>
<text id="74001800">Ah, thou'st... A Divine Spear become!</text>
<text id="74001801">An honour once bestowed in the time of the Gods, nearly unheard of in this age of waning fire.</text>
<text id="74001802">As a servant of the Princess, and friend to Midir...</text>
<text id="74001803">I am honoured to have met thee.</text>
<text id="74001900">As the fire waneth, does she lie by the dark, but now with thee to shelter her sleep.</text>
<text id="74001901">Bless ye divine spears. May thy travels be resplendent with glory.</text>
<text id="74002000">I've searched for thee, dark-stricken creature.</text>
<text id="74002001">I am Shira, daughter of the Duke, descendant of gods, and trusted friend to Midir.</text>
<text id="74002002">At once, I am the honour of the gods, the glory of fire, and the fear of the dark.</text>
<text id="74002003">Thou shalt not go unpunished.</text>
<text id="74002004">For thy treachery, thy profanity, and thy shameless yearning!</text>
<text id="74002100">Remember this, creature.</text>
<text id="74002101">Ne'er will I forgive thy kind.</text>
<text id="74002200">Try again, to remember.</text>
<text id="74002201">The great honour it was to be a spear.</text>
<text id="74002300"></text>
<text id="74002301"></text>
<text id="74002302"></text>
<text id="74002303"></text>
<text id="74002400"></text>
<text id="74002500">Ahh, but why...</text>
<text id="74002501">Art thou to bed with the dark?</text>
<text id="74002600">Never would I ever...</text>
<text id="74002601">...forgive thy lowly kind...</text>
<text id="75000000">Many of us are by the fire forsaken.</text>
<text id="75000001">I speak of thine kind, and mine.</text>
<text id="75000002">Behold this city! We are kindred, belike two eyes which gaze upon the other.</text>
<text id="75000003">Fear not, the dark, my friend.</text>
<text id="75000004">And let the feast begin.</text>
<text id="75000100">One met the dark with learning. But in the end, learned his knowledge was wanting.</text>
<text id="75000101">The world began without knowledge, and without knowledge will it end.</text>
<text id="75000102">Dost not this ring clear and true?</text>
<text id="75000103">Fear not, the dark, my friend.</text>
<text id="75000104">And let the feast begin.</text>
<text id="75000200">One poor girl slew her own kin, but even so, was embraced, enveloped by the Abyss.</text>
<text id="75000201">Twas a comfort that neither moon nor sunless sky afforded her before.</text>
<text id="75000202">Fear not, the dark, my friend.</text>
<text id="75000203">And let the feast begin.</text>
<text id="75000300">One was a wayfaring knight, on an endless, forbidden search.</text>
<text id="75000301">Only the Abyss granted closure, if not reunion with his beloved.</text>
<text id="75000302">Fear not, the dark, my friend.</text>
<text id="75000303">And let the feast begin.</text>
<text id="75000400">And so, she lived in fear. Of the dark, of the things that gnawed at her flesh.</text>
<text id="75000401">And yet! The Abyss hath yet to produce any such creature!</text>
<text id="75000402">Fear not, the dark, my friend.</text>
<text id="75000403">And let the feast begin.</text>
<text id="75000500">And so, despite his weighty armour, he lived in fear. Of a delicate thing, little more than a girl.</text>
<text id="75000501">Where fire resideth, shadows twist and shrivel. But in the Abyss, there are shadows none.</text>
<text id="75000502">Fear not, the dark, my friend.</text>
<text id="75000503">And let the feast begin.</text>
<text id="75000600">Of all the Fingers, he alone was embraced by the Abyss.</text>
<text id="75000601">For he was human, and ne'er a grub.</text>
<text id="75000602">Fear not, the dark, my friend.</text>
<text id="75000603">And let the feast begin.</text>
<text id="75000700">Ahh, yes, yes, I remember now!</text>
<text id="75000701">Let the feast begin.</text>
<text id="75000702">Let the feast begin.</text>
<text id="75000800">I shall partake!</text>
<text id="75000900"></text>
<text id="75001000"></text>
<text id="75001001"></text>
<text id="75001002"></text>
<text id="75001003"></text>
<text id="75001100"></text>
<text id="75001200">Search thine own self. Fear not the dark.</text>
<text id="75001201">And let the feast begin.</text>
<text id="76000000">Oh, your head's square on your shoulders, is it?</text>
<text id="76000001">I thought that clamouring tin can was the last, but here we go again.</text>
<text id="76000002">What is it you want from this old stone-humped hag?</text>
<text id="76000003">I've nothing for you, not a smithereen. I just like to stand here, and take in the view.</text>
<text id="76000100">Well, that came out of nowhere.</text>
<text id="76000101">You think an old stone-humped hag would be brimming with goodies?</text>
<text id="76000102">I've none of that, not a smithereen.</text>
<text id="76000200">Strange little lad, you are.</text>
<text id="76000201">Strange little lass, you are.</text>
<text id="76000202">What on earth do you see in me?</text>
<text id="76000300">At the close of the Age of Fire, all lands meet at the end of the earth.</text>
<text id="76000301">Great kingdoms and anaemic townships will be one and the same.
The great tide of human enterprise, all for naught.</text>
<text id="76000302">That's why I'm so taken by this grand sight.</text>
<text id="76000303">This must be what it's like to be a god.</text>
<text id="76000400">Oh, if you just can't stop yourself, at least hear this.</text>
<text id="76000401">Far below, there's a deep, dark hole carved out of a tree.</text>
<text id="76000402">...From time to time, voices brim from the depths of the cavity even now.</text>
<text id="76000403">Mutterings of the very demon that Prince Lorian spoke of, I'm sure.</text>
<text id="76000404">Horrible sounds, of an afflicted thing yet cursing men.</text>
<text id="76000500">Why, where did you hear that name, love?</text>
<text id="76000501">Oh, it doesn't matter. I'll tell you what I know.</text>
<text id="76000502">The Ringed City is said to be at world's end.</text>
<text id="76000503">Past this heap of rubbish, as far as one can go.</text>
<text id="76000504">But you'd better think twice.</text>
<text id="76000505">The forsaken Ringed City was walled off by the gods to contain the pygmies.</text>
<text id="76000506">...and the dark soul is better left well alone...</text>
<text id="76000600">Ahh, yes, it's just what you'd guess.</text>
<text id="76000601">Legend says that the Ringed City lies at the end of the earth.</text>
<text id="76000602">This heap of everything, you're looking right at it.</text>
<text id="76000603">But be warned.</text>
<text id="76000604">The pygmies were exiled to the Ringed City.
And no one should go near the dark soul.</text>
<text id="76000700">You're not willing to reconsider, are you?</text>
<text id="76000701">Well, that's just fine. It's a rare thing, to have a true duty.</text>
<text id="76000702">Don't go and take it for granted, I suppose.</text>
<text id="76000703">Won't do any better than this, not you or that poor tin can.</text>
<text id="76000800">Keep your marbles intact, love.</text>
<text id="76000801">At least until I lose mine.</text>
<text id="76000900">When you see that tin can, pass the word along.</text>
<text id="76000901">I'm afraid he's a little too brave for his own good.</text>
<text id="76001000">Don't run off and die, love.</text>
<text id="76001001">It's a nicer view with you in it.</text>
<text id="76001100"></text>
<text id="76001101"></text>
<text id="76001102"></text>
<text id="76001103"></text>
<text id="76001200"></text>
<text id="76001300">My time has come, has it?</text>
<text id="76001301">Well, maybe I'll get to see an angel.</text>
<text id="77000000">Hark! They brought thee here, did they not?</text>
<text id="77000001">Dost thou the gods serve? Or merely that role affect?</text>
<text id="77000100"></text>
<text id="77000101">A lie, a wretched lie! How wouldst one such as thee do service to the gods?</text>
<text id="77000102">Thy scheme is known to me, I know what it is thou desirest.</text>
<text id="77000103">...The dark soul, no?</text>
<text id="77000104">Why else wouldst one deign to visit this dung heap?</text>
<text id="77000105">Give rest to thy falsity, I would be an ally to thee.</text>
<text id="77000106"></text>
<text id="77000200">Yes, yes, of course. How wouldst one such as thee do service to the gods?</text>
<text id="77000201">I have intimate knowledge of thy kind. I know thy want.</text>
<text id="77000202">...The dark soul, is it not?</text>
<text id="77000203">Why else wouldst one deign to visit this dung heap?</text>
<text id="77000204">Give rest to thy falsity, I would be an ally to thee.</text>
<text id="77000205"></text>
<text id="77000300">If it is the dark soul thou desirest...</text>
<text id="77000301">Then seek Filianore's church, at the base of the cliff.</text>
<text id="77000302">There wilt thou the sleeping Princess waken.</text>
<text id="77000303">...Her slumber is a deceit...</text>
<text id="77000304">A lid covering an overgrown privy; a prop to keep thee from the dark soul of thine desire.</text>
<text id="77000400"></text>
<text id="77000401">Worry not, I am a true friend to thee.</text>
<text id="77000402">If thou'rt yet human, the urge will soon begin to swell.</text>
<text id="77000403">To curse the gods, and bring ruin upon this accursed heap of dung.</text>
<text id="77000404"></text>
<text id="77000500">Now, yarely to Filianore's church at the base of the cliff, to rouse the sleeping Princess.</text>
<text id="77000501">If thou yet the dark soul desirest...</text>
<text id="77000502"></text>
<text id="77000600">Ahh, I prithee help...</text>
<text id="77000601">The Red-hood is come to eat us...</text>
<text id="77000602">To eat our dark souls...</text>
<text id="77000700"></text>
<text id="77000701"></text>
<text id="77000702"></text>
<text id="77000703"></text>
<text id="77000800"></text>
<text id="77000801">May the Abyss's curse take the gods....</text>
<text id="77000900">Ohh, Filianore, help me, please...</text>
<text id="77000901">The Red-hood is come to eat us...</text>
<text id="77000902">To eat our dark souls...</text>
<text id="77001000">Filianore...help me, please...</text>
<text id="78000000">Unknowing visitor, return from whence thou camest.</text>
<text id="78000001">The Abyss runneth deep. By the King's decree,</text>
<text id="78000002">None may disturb our mistress's slumber.</text>
<text id="78000100">Turn back, unknowing visitor.</text>
<text id="78000101">By the King's decree.</text>
<text id="78000200">Foolishness. The King's decree is no trifling matter.</text>
<text id="78000201">I, Judicator Argo, shall deliver thee justice.</text>
<text id="78000202">...Spear of the Church, sworn defender of our Princess Filianore!</text>
<text id="78000203">Harken to the call that summons thee!</text>
<text id="78000204">Make haste!</text>
<text id="78000300">Spear of the church, by the sacred decree, protect our Princess.</text>
<text id="78000400"></text>
<text id="78000401"></text>
<text id="78000402"></text>
<text id="78000403"></text>
<text id="78000500"></text>
<text id="78000600"></text>
<text id="78000601">Spear of the Church, make haste...</text>
<text id="78000700">Spear of the Church, turn back.</text>
<text id="78000701">The Abyss runneth deep. Thou'rt sworn to protect our mistress's slumber.</text>
<text id="78000702">Or wouldst thou thy covenant forsake, in violation of the King's decree?</text>
<text id="78000800">Turn back, Spear of the Church.</text>
<text id="78000801">Or wouldst thou thy covenant forsake, in violation of the King's decree?</text>
<text id="78000900">Foolishness. To forswear thy covenant and the King's decree.</text>
<text id="78000901">I, Judicator Argo, shall bring this defiled spear to justice.</text>
<text id="78000902">...Divine spear of Yore, sworn defender of our Princess Filianore!</text>
<text id="78000903">Harken to the call that summons thee.</text>
<text id="78000904">Make haste!</text>
<text id="78001000">Divine spear of yore, by sacred decree, protect our dear Princess...</text>
<text id="78001100"></text>
<text id="78001101">Divine spear of yore, make haste...</text>
</entries>
</fmg>